<mvc:View controllerName="myapp.controller.App"
    displayBlock="true"
    xmlns:mvc="sap.ui.core.mvc"
    xmlns="sap.m">

    <VBox class="aboutUsPageVBox" alignItems="Center" width="100%">
        <Title id="aboutUsPage" text="About Us" level="H1" class="aboutUsTitle"/>
        <VBox width="80%" class="aboutUsPanel">
            <Text id="aboutUsText" class="aboutUsText"
                text="LTI Life Insurance is committed to providing innovative and reliable insurance solutions to protect you and your loved ones.

With a strong legacy of trust and customer focus, we offer a wide range of life insurance products tailored to meet your unique needs.

Our mission is to ensure financial security and peace of mind for our customers through transparent processes and dedicated service.

We believe in building lasting relationships and empowering individuals and families to plan confidently for the future.

Our experienced team is always ready to assist you in making informed decisions about your insurance needs."/>
            <Text id="aboutUsText3" class="aboutUsText" 
                text="Our products are designed to offer flexibility, affordability, and peace of mind.

At LTI Life Insurance, we are more than just an insurance provider; we are your trusted partner in securing your future.

We continuously strive to enhance our services and products to meet the evolving needs of our customers.

Experience the difference with LTI Life Insurance, where your protection is our priority.
We are committed to providing you with the best insurance solutions and exceptional customer service.
Our team of experts is dedicated to guiding you through every step of your insurance journey, ensuring that you have the right coverage for your needs.
We understand that life is full of uncertainties, and we are here to help you navigate them with confidence.
Whether you are looking for life insurance, health insurance, or investment options, we have a solution for you.
Our policies are designed to provide you with financial security and peace of mind, so you can focus on what matters most to you.
Join us at LTI Life Insurance and experience the difference.
We are committed to building a better future for you and your family, one policy at a time.
Thank you for choosing LTI Life Insurance as your trusted insurance partner.
"/>
        </VBox>
    </VBox>
</mvc:View>